The  Bells
“八爪蜘蛛”
Come in.
And?
Nothing?
She won't eat.
We'll try again at supper.
I think they're watching me.
- Who? - Her soldiers.
Of course they are. That's their job.
What have I told you, Martha?
The greater the risk, the greater the reward.
Go on. They'll be missing you in the kitchen.
“小恶魔” 丹妮莉丝的女王之手
The Northern armies?
Just crossed the Trident.
They'll be at the walls of King's Landing in two days.
How is she?
She hasn't seen anyone since we returned.
Hasn't left her chambers, hasn't accepted any food.
She shouldn't be alone.
You're worried for her. I admire your empathy.
Aren't you worried for her?
I'm worried for all of us.
They say every time a Targaryen is born,
the gods toss a coin and the world holds its breath.
We're not much for riddles where I'm from.
We both know what she's about to do.
伊耿·坦格利安 铁王座法理继承人
That's her decision to make. She is our queen.
Men decide where power resides, whether or not they know it.
What do you want?
All I've ever wanted.
The right ruler on the Iron Throne.
I still don't know how her coin has landed.
But I'm quite certain about yours.
I don't want it.
I never have.
I have known more kings and queens than any man living.
I've heard what they say to crowds,
and seen what they do in the shadows.
I have furthered their designs, however horrible.
But what I tell you now is true:
You will rule wisely and well, while she--
She...
is my queen.
Your Grace?
There's something you need to know.
“风暴降生”“龙之母”
Someone has betrayed me.
Yes.
Jon Snow.
Varys.
He knows the truth about Jon.
He does.
Because you told him.
You learned from Sansa.
And she learned from Jon,
though I begged him not to tell her.
As I said...
he betrayed me.
I'm glad Sansa told me.
I am your Hand.
I need to be aware of any threats you're facing.
And Varys?
Your Master of Whisperers needs to be aware too.
You spoke to him first.
Without coming to me.
Without asking my permission.
It was a mistake.
Why do you think Sansa told you?
What do you think she hoped to gain?
- She trusts me. - Yes, she trusts you.
She trusted you to spread secrets
that could destroy your own queen.
And you did not let her down.
If I have failed you, my queen, forgive me.
Our intentions were good.
We wanted what you want. A better world, all of us.
Varys as much as anyone.
But it doesn't matter now.
No.
It doesn't matter now.
无垢者指挥官
It was me.
I hope I deserve this.
Truly, I do.
I hope I'm wrong.
Goodbye, old friend.
Lord Varys.
I, Daenerys of House Targaryen,
First of My Name,
Breaker of Chains and Mother of Dragons...
sentence you to die.
丹妮莉丝的黑龙
Dracarys.
This was all she brought with her
when we crossed the Narrow Sea.
Her only possession.
What did I say would happen if you told your sister?
I don't want it, and that's what I told him.
She betrayed your trust.
She killed Varys as much as I did.
This was a victory for her.
Now she knows what happens
when people hear the truth about you.
Far more people in Westeros love you than love me.
I don't have love here.
I only have fear.
I love you.
And you will always be my queen.
Is that all I am to you?
Your queen?
All right, then.
Let it be fear.
The people who live there, they're not your enemies.
They're innocents, like the ones you liberated in Meereen.
In Meereen, the slaves turned on the masters
and liberated the city themselves the moment I arrived.
They're afraid.
Anyone who resists Cersei
will see his family butchered.
You can't expect them to be heroes.
- They're hostages. - They are.
In a tyrant's grip. Whose fault is that? Mine?
What does it matter whose fault it is?
Thousands of children will die if the city burns.
Your sister knows how to use
her enemies' weaknesses against them.
That's what she thinks our mercy is:
weakness.
- I beg you, my queen - But she's wrong.
Mercy is our strength.
Our mercy towards future generations
who will never again be held hostage by a tyrant.
Ready the Unsullied.
Tonight you sail for King's Landing
- to join the Northern armies. - Cersei's followers
will abandon her if they know the war is lost.
Give them that chance.
If the city surrenders,
they will ring the bells and raise the gates.
Please, if you hear them ringing the bells, call off the attack.
Wait for me outside the city.
You'll know when it's time.
Your brother was stopped trying to get past our lines.
It seems he hasn't abandoned your sister after all.
The next time you fail me...
will be the last time you fail me.
Let them pass.
Through the gate.
The rearguard should be here by daybreak.
She wants to attack now.
“洋葱骑士”
Daybreak at the earliest.
Davos.
I need to ask you a favor.
You're the greatest smuggler alive, aren't you?
I'm not gonna like this favor, am I?
Ay up. Where you going?
“猎狗”
I'm Arya Stark.
I'm going to kill Queen Cersei.
Think about it.
She kills Cersei, the war's over.
There won't be a siege.You might not even die tomorrow.
I need to go talk to my captain.
Go ahead, talk to him.
Where's he going?
We speak the common tongue.
Ah. Good.
I want to be alone with the prisoner.
Get some rest. Tomorrow will be a long day.
We have orders to guard the prisoner.
Ordered by whom? The queen herself?
- No. - Well, in that case,
as Hand of the Queen, I outrank whomever gave your order.
Probably by quite a lot.
“弑君者”
How did they find you?
Did you consider taking it off?
Cersei once called me "the stupidest Lannister."
And you're going back to her, to die with her.
You've underestimated her before.
She's going to die.
Unless you can convince her
to change her course of action.
Difficult to do from here.
When have I ever been able to convince Cersei of anything?
Try.
If not for yourself, if not for her,
then for every one of the million people in that city,
innocent or otherwise.
To be honest, I never really cared much for them.
Innocent or otherwise.
You do care for one innocent.
I know you do.
And so does Cersei.
She has a reason now.
The child is the reason she'll never give an inch.
All the worst things she's ever done,
she's done for her children.
It's not impossible that she'll win.
She won't.
Her enemy's forces have been depleted,
as she said they would be.
Two of the three dragons are dead.
- She's evened the odds. - The city will fall tomorrow.
She has the Lannister army, she has the Golden Company--
I defended the city last time it was attacked.
I know it better than anyone. It will fall tomorrow.
Then I suppose I'll die tomorrow, if not before.
Why?
Escape.
The two of you, together.
Remember where we met,
where they keep the dragon skulls,
beneath the Red Keep?
Take her down there.
Keep following the stairways down,
down as far as they'll go.
You'll come out onto a beach at the foot of the keep.
A dinghy will be waiting for you.
Sail out of the bay.
If the winds are kind, you'll make it to Pentos.
Start a new life.
Sail right past the Iron Fleet and into a new life?
Sounds a lot less likely than Cersei winning this war--
There won't be an Iron Fleet for much longer.
Do it.
If you don't, you'll never see Cersei again.
Swear to me.
You have my word.
If it works,
give the order to ring all the bells
in King's Landing and open the gates.
That will be our signal that the city has surrendered.
I'll try.
I never thought I'd get to repay the favor.
Remember, ring the bells and open the gates.
Your queen will execute you for this.
If Daenerys can make it to the throne
without wading through a river of blood,
maybe she'll show mercy
to the person who made that possible.
Tens of thousands of innocent lives...
one not particularly innocent dwarf...
it seems like a fair trade.
If it weren't for you,
I never would've survived my childhood.
You would have.
You were the only one
who didn't treat me like a monster.
You were all I had.
铁群岛之王
Eyes on the horizon!
Load the scorpion!
Archers, close up!
Come on!
Up to the espringal!
To the back of it!
Archers, line up!
This way! Come on!
Clear the streets now!
- No! - In, now.
- And you, come on. - Inside, now!
Quickly.
Yes. Follow down there.
They're here. Get to the Red Keep.
- My son! - Get inside!
Just ahead of you, I can see it!
All right, move it!
- Come on! - Keep moving!
- Keep going! - Keep moving!
- Quickly! - All the way!
- Come on! - Come on!
Hold your mother's hand!
Make way for the Golden Company!
Close the gate!
黄金团团长
If you hear the bells ring, they've surrendered.
Call off your men.
Move along now, lads.
铁王座上的女王
- That's it. - Go on, move it.
Come on, move, move. Faster, faster. Come on, move it.
- Keep going. - Keep moving.
- Move. - Stay with him.
- Hold on. - Hold my hand.
Get behind there.
Close the gate!
No more through.
- No. - No. Mommy.
- Vicky! Please! - No, please, sir!
- Open the gate! - Close the gate!
- Open it! - Open the gate!
- Get back. - Look, try that one. Go. Go.
The gates are locked now!
Open!
- Get back! - Open the gate!
Soldier! Soldier!
- Please open the gate! - Go back to your homes!
Stay back! It's closed!
Soldier!
Move away! Stop!
Let us in!
We're not leaving!
Turn!
Turn it around!
Get back! Back!
Fire!
I can see her!
Ready!
Move!
Fire!
- Reload! - Reload!
Faster!
Hurry!
Fire!
Go!
Run!
Your Grace.
All we need is one good shot.
The scorpions have all been destroyed, Your Grace.
被剥夺项链的学士 瑟曦的女王之手
“魔山”
The Iron Fleet hold Blackwater Bay.
Euron killed one of her dragons.
He can kill another.
Your Grace, the Iron Fleet is burning.
The gates have been breached.
The Golden Company--
Our men will fight harder than sellswords ever could.
They will defend their queen to the last man.
- Yes, Your Grace. - The Red Keep has never fallen.
It won't fall today.
No, no, no!
Move, move!
Run.
Run!
Come on!
- Ring the bells! - Ring the bells!
The bells!
Ring the bloody bells!
- Ring the bells! - Ring the bells!
Tell the queen to ring the bells.
Ring the bells! Ring the bell!
This way.
Ring the bell!
Ring them!
Ring the bells!
- Ring the bells! - Help us!
In the name of the--
Queen! We're surrounded!
- Ring the bells! - Now! Come on!
Hurry up!
Ring the bells!
No!
Get back!
Stay! Stay!
No, no, no, no, no.
Quickly. Quickly.
Stop!
- Get off me! Get off, bitch! - No, get off! Help! Help!
No!
Go!
Find somewhere to hide.
My God!
The Kingslayer.
We need to get the queen out of King's Landing.
Listen.
That's the sound of a city dying.
It's over.
Well, maybe for you.
If you kill another king before you die...
they'll sing about you forever.
You're no king.
Oh, but I am.
And I fucked the queen.
If I win...
I'll bring your head to Cersei
so you can kiss her one last time.
Your Grace, it isn't safe here any longer.
The Red Keep is the safest place in the city.
The Unsullied have breached the gates of the Red Keep.
Maegor's Holdfast would be a better place
to wait out the storm.
You fought well...
for a cripple.
Another king for you.
But I got you!
I got you!
I'm the man who killed Jaime Lannister.
Go home, girl.
The fire will get her,
or one of the Dothraki.
Or maybe that dragon will eat her.
It doesn't matter. She's dead.
And you'll be dead too if you don't get out of here.
I'm going to kill her.
You think you wanted revenge a long time?
I've been after it all my life.
It's all I care about.
And look at me. Look at me!
You wanna be like me?
You come with me, you die here.
Sandor.
Thank you.
Your Grace.
Hello, big brother.
Ser Gregor, stay by my side.
Ser Gregor, I command you.
Obey your queen, Ser Gregor.
Yeah, that's you.
That's what you've always been.
You're hurt.
It doesn't matter.
You're bleeding.
Alanna!
Alanna! Have you seen my wife?
Have you seen my wife?
Out of the way!
No!
Oh.
Take my hand.
Get up. Get up.
- No. No.- Wait! Wait!
No!
Fucking die!
We need to fall back!
Fall back behind the wall!
- Fall back!- Fall back!
Get out of the city!
Fall back!
- Fall back!- Fall back!
You can't stay here.
You have to keep moving.
We can't go out there.
You have to.
Everyone out there is dead.
If you stay here, you'll die.
Follow me.
Follow me!
Come on, quickly. Come to me.
Lean him up there.
Come on, quickly. All of you!
Run!
Mama!
Mama! No.
Mama! Mama!
Mama!
Get up.
Get up!
We have to keep moving.
Take her.
Take her!
- Take her.- Come on!
Come on!
This way.
I want our baby to live.
Don't let me die, Jaime.Please don't let me die.
It's all right.
- Please don't let me die.- It's all right.
I don't want to die.
Just look-- Look at me.
- Look at me.- Not like this.
Not like this. Not like this.
Look-- Look-- Look me in the eye.
Don't look away. Don't look--
Look at me! Just look at me.
Nothing else matters.
Only us.